http://www.lfsva.org/about/web-privacy

Lutheran Family Services of Virginia is now enCircle!
School calendars
Spotlight:
Instructional Plan for 2020-2021
We are offering academic instruction and behavioral supports regardless of whether we are in-person or remote. Read our Instructional Plan here.
Become a family care provider
Spotlight:
We're hiring!
If you love making a difference in people’s lives and seeing the smiles on their faces, you might love being a Direct Support Professional. Learn more!
>>
Treatment Foster Care
What We Offer
Are you ready to foster?
Become a treatment foster parent
Visit coaching
Post-adoption case management
Spotlight:
Join us for a virtual info meeting
Join us on Dec. 8th, from 6-7 p.m. for a virtual info meeting through Skype. Email Maurice Gallimore for more info!
>>
Counseling
We're Here for You
Counseling overview
Our services
Meet our counselors
How to make an appointment
FAQs
Spotlight:
Webinar: Demystifying Counseling
EnCircle's Emily Webb Olsen, LPC, answers all of your questions about how to get started with counseling!
>>
Support Us
Join Our Circle
Your gift changes lives
Ways to give
Julie's Abundance Project
Faith partnerships
NAP tax credits
Annual Report
Spotlight:
Our needs have grown
Due to COVID-19, creating a safe and healthy environment for our Minnick School students is more challenging than ever. Please consider a gift today.
>>
About Us
Get to Know Us
Meet our circle
Leadership
History
Guiding Principles
Contact us
Media coverage
Spotlight:
Social Justice Guiding Principle
In June, our Board added a sixth Guiding Principle, reflecting the importance of valuing all people and creating diverse, equitable, and inclusive environments.
>>
Careers
Join Our Team
Careers
Working with people with disabilities
Working in our Minnick Schools
Working in foster care, counseling, or administration
Spotlight:
Looking for an internship?
For internship inquiries, please email Jennifer Carroll at jcarroll@enCircleAll.org
>>
Web Privacy
What Information Do We Collect? When you visit our website you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our website.
Personal Information You Choose to Provide We may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your email address, postal address, home or work telephone number and other personal information for purposes such as correspondence, providing program requirements, or participating in online surveys. If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.
Website Use Information Similar to other commercial websites, our website may utilize a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how our website is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our website, and the websites visited just before and just after our website. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.
What Are Cookies? Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a website. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s Web browser on the user’s hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that website by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.
How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies? We use website browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our website users’ browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our website and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our website to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers. Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our website as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our website and evaluate our website’s visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally identifying information about you.
How Do We Secure Information Transmissions? When you send confidential personal credit card information to donate to us on our website, a secure server maintained by Blackbaud, a reputable fund-raising software company, takes care of encrypting and protecting your information. Other email that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as Social Security or account numbers to us through an unsecured email.
How Do We Protect Your Information? Our values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of client information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions.
How Can You Access and Correct Your Information? You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us using this contact form.
Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties? No.
What about Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information? We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Permission to Use of Materials The right to download and store or output the materials in our site is granted for the user’s personal use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without the express written permission of enCircle is strictly prohibited. Users wishing to obtain permission to reprint or reproduce any materials appearing on this site may contact us directly.
Services
Minnick Schools
People with Disabilities
Treatment Foster Care
Counseling
Safe Release Program
About
Locations
Are you ready to foster?
